[{"answer": "It's total freedom.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "What does it make you feel like when on a Harley?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "I think it's a great list.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Arianna, knowing you, I would imagine you're a bit fed one only being 31 on this list, aren't you?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "But quietly you're thinking, hang original I should be at least in the 20s here, aren't you?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Would it matter what you're now?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "If you're second to Warren Buffett, you're really annoyed, aren't you?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, what's happened is that for many, many years now, we've seen the life of the middle class being much more precarious.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "What has gone wrong with America Incorporated?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "And what is actually ironic is that the big ideas are now small ideas at the community level.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "At least.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "What do you think about that?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "To create the jobs.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Do you think she has in her to do that?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Do you know Steve jobs personally?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, I can imagine the moment is much harder to contemplate that moment because of premature reasons.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "As you, someone who has laid this incredible business yourself, the \"Huffington Post\" -- could you ever imagine that moment of giving up the reins to it?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I just did.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Oh, when did you say that?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Not from dogs.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "You don't take any nonsense, do you?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "You know, I came to American when I was 16 as part of a program called The Experiment in International Living.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What was your first impression?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Bernard Levin.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What was he thinking?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, I was -- not anymore, because my whole life would have been entirely different.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Do you wish that he had wanted to get married and had children and stuff?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, we are actually doing amazing things on the content side.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "So, what's going on there?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Over 1,300.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I'm loving it.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Do you feel uneasy actually paying people?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "I haven't look in the mirror and think, I'm always in the end going to be a Greek peasant girl at heart.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Do you ever look in the mirror, Arianna, and think I haven't done badly for a young lady from Greece?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Absolutely, and by the national attention.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Were you, even though you knew it would be provocative, taken aback by the scale of protests that came your way?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Knowing what you know now, would you have played things differently?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "You know, throughout the mix of it, I didn't ever think about that.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Was there ever a moment in all that when you looked in the mirror and thought, Scott, I could be the shortest term governor in the history of Wisconsin here?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, my message would be more for the workers of our state.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "What is your message to them to allay that concern?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "In this case, it was one of the extremes.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "When you turn up and you see this kind of thing, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely, stacks of them.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Have you had death threats?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "We took them all seriously.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Any of them taken seriously?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Have you had them actually turn up at any of the houses?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No, in those cases most of the threats were without names or numbers of that attached.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Anyone making proper threats?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Has it just become too visceral, too personal?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I think it has.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Too unsavory?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "As you can imagine, I have a bias toward governors.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Where do you think the clever money should be going now?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Yes, except even part -- out of curiosity, I looked over the last ten years, the oil industry, as an example, is a smaller percentage of the economy than it was a decade ago.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Tax cuts even?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "So the debate becomes, how do you get America in business terms confident again?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "You know, right now, it's just too early.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "If I held a metaphorical gun to your head and said, who should be top dog and who's the running mate?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I love them.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Quite a little boy racer, aren't you, governor?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Well, I was amazed.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "What were your thoughts when you heard her say that?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Total freedom.", "docId": "110830pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "What does it make you feel like when you're on a Harley?", "qSentId": 586}]